# Marco Antonio V Montoya



Montreal, Canada



+1(514)209 5032



marcovmontoya.me



MarcoVMontoya1989



marcovmontoya@protonmail.com

#### PROFILE

Professional developer with 5 years of experience in web development, specialized in ReactJS, JavaScript frameworks. Always combining my passion for programming & technology I'm a self-driven person, committed to achieving results, with keen eye for details, looking for the best solution to problems with best code practices.

### EXPERIENCE

## Software Engineer FrontEnd, Mexico City

June 2017 - April 2019 LINIO REGIONAL LATAM

Working in FrontEnd and BackEnd team in charge to create new features to improve, integrate the content and new features of the website, debugging and improving the UI experience, improving API for mobile team,

creating new features to have impact on purchaces, reviewing code form other developers, unit test, also I worked for other clients to maintain Hewlett Packard, Banco Pacifico (Ecuador), Club Premier, Avianca Lifemiles using the Linio template.

## Windows Azure Consultant & Developer, Mexico City

October 2015 - November 2016 CLOUD CONTINUITY SYSTEMS SERVICES

Responsible of developing web pages (mainly web design with C# and ASP.NET) to implement the Cloud Services using Azure Websites Services API.

## Intern Consultant & Software Developer, Mexico City

August 2014 – February 2015 CLOUD CONTINUITY SYSTEMS SERVICES

Responsible in the participation of CSP projects with Azure in the creation of demos from Azure Portal.

#### EDUCATION

# **AEC Web Design and Programming - CDI College Montreal**

August 2019 – February 2021 AEC COLLEGE DEGREE

# **Project Management Specialization - Panamerican University Mexico**

August 2014 - July 2015 BACHELOR OF ENGINEERING SPECIALIZAITION

## Information Technology and Intelligent Systems Engineer - Panamerican University Mexico

August 2009 - July 2014 BACHELOR OF ENGINEERING

SKILLS

JavaScript	React	NodeJS	Git	Photoshop
PHP	Redux	Express	CSS	Illustrator
TDD	MySQL	Bootstrap	SASS	
OOP	MongoDB	Tailwind	HTML5	
FP	Mongoose	ThreeJS		

## LANGUAGES

Spanish - Native

English - Professional Proficiency

OTHER

Hearing Loss - Use of Cochlear implant.

# HOBBY

VideoGames, Cinema, Books, Swimming, Trading Cards Game, Board Game, Dogs.